Into the night
Desperate and broken
The sound of a fight
Father has spoken
We were the kings and queens
of promise
We were the victims of ourselves
Maybe the children of a lesser God
Between Heaven and Hell
Heaven and Hell
Into your eyes
Hopeless and taken
We stole our new lives
Through blood and pain
In defense
of our dreams
We were the Kings
and Queens of promise
We were the victims
of ourselves
Maybe the Children
of a lesser God
Between Heaven and Hell
Heaven and Hell
The age of man is over
A darkness comes and all
These lessons that
we learned here
Have only just begun
We were the Kings
and Queens of promise
We were the victims of ourselves
Maybe the Children
of a lesser God
Between Heaven and Hell
We are the Kings
We are the queens
We are the
queens